{
    "id": "9faa4289e376452bb22a5eddeb30232e",
    "title": "Completing sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9a2e8c6e6a0247d2bac4fa797febad1d",
            "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He began to play guitar when he ............................... six.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He started talking about his pet projects, but everybody ................................... out of the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "goes",
                        "went",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I looked out of the window and saw Susie ..................................... down the street.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to drive",
                        "driving",
                        "drove"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My legs were stiff because I ......................................... standing still for a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "have been",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wondered who ................................... the money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "took",
                        "has taken",
                        "had taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "After he finished his exams, he .................................. to New York for a month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "goes",
                        "went",
                        "has gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We eat that we ..................................... live.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "must",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I donâ€™t know ............................... she will come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "whether",
                        "weather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If they ..................................... him to a good hospital, he would have survived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have taken",
                        "took",
                        "had taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the girl ...................................... won the first prize.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "which",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}